[thunder rumbling]
[loud thunderclap crashing]
[Oz] I ever tell you
about Rex Calabrese?
[Victor] Uh, no.
He ran my neighborhood
when I was a kid.
[distant siren wailing]
Had this, uh, gold Cadillac
with white leather seats.
- [fire roars]
- [Oz chuckles]
Beautiful.
When it rolled down your street,
I mean, it felt like your block
was blessed.
Rex's ride,
it wasn't just a car,
it was a fuckin' chariot.
Made a kid with a bum leg
feel like even he could be king.
[chuckles]
- The end of an era.
- [thunder crashing]
[rain pattering]
[Oz] Come on.
[Victor] Uh, what about Sofia?
- Now that she knows--
- Sofia?
Ah, chick's a thorn
without a prick, kid.
We get our shrooms back,
she won't matter.
Right.
- Sorry, Oz.
- For what?
For wrecking your chariot.
I only got one shot at this.
You know, I-I see that now.
You came back, Vic.
Put your ass on the line for me.
A hundred Maseratis
couldn't replace that.
Though this one came
pretty damn close.
It's you and me now, kid.
Till the end.
Ain't it time we get ourselves
some goddamn respect?
Huh?
- Let's fucking go.
- [laughs]
- I like that.
- [chuckles]
Alright. Here's our ride.
[whistles]
[car horn honks]
[Oz] Welcome to the party,
fellas!
Oz, your fuckin' car.
Ah, what are you gonna do?
Only the good die young.
So, listen. When I eat, you eat.
How it's always been, right?
- Yeah, 'course.
- Alright, good.
Well I got somethin'
beautiful going.
A new drug. Homegrown.
I was gonna cut you in on it,
but fuckin' Maronis took it
off my plate before I could.
So, how we getting it back?
- [explosion booming]
- Whoa.
[Oz] Hey, listen.
The Maronis got a huge
fuckin' blind spot
just beggin' to be exploited.
Come here, look at this.
Yo, what up, fam.
I'm getting a slick new
back piece
from the Chicano
legend himself--
- [Oz] Taj Maroni.
- [laughter]
This is the heir to
Sal's throne.
...to tell all you
motherfuckers the Maronis
are about to take back
what was taken from us.
This stupid motherfucker,
he's just beggin' to be got.
["Note Siah" by Farshad playing]
[muffled gunfire]
- [splattering]
- [body thuds]
- [music stops]
- [Oz] Hey!
[Taj] Yo, what the fuck?
- Mikey!
- [Mikey] I got him!
[dramatic, frenetic music
playing]
[Mikey] Don't you fuckin'--
[Victor] Stop!
[Taj grunts]
Hey. Hey.
Hold still, you piece of shit.
Oh, you are so fucked, man.
You messed with the wrong
fuckin' family!
My-My mother, my father,
they won't stand for this--
That's what I'm countin' on.
[ominous music playing]
[cell doors whir, clang]
[distant buzzer sounds]
[distant indistinct chatter]
[music fades]
[distant buzzer sounds]
What do you want?
I want what's mine.
What your wife stole from me.
I want my fuckin' shrooms.
Our son is not a pawn.
There is a code.
Oh, is that right?
What, I take the wrong
Maroni? That it?
[bangs table] You do not
threaten my family.
Jesus, Sal.
Put your dick away.
Don't forget who I got at home.
[Salvatore grumbles]
We meet early, before sunrise,
for the exchange.
Make sure my shrooms
are ready to go.
And what do you say we keep it
nice and intimate?
Just you, me, and Taj.
No. My wife doesn't go alone.
Fine. I'll let you take
one guard, Nadia.
- 'Cause I'm a gentleman.
- [scoffs]
Sal.
[in Farsi]
Hey!
Honor your end,
and Taj will be just fine.
Now...
we got a deal or what?
- [buzzer sounds]
- [lock clicks]
[man over PA]
All security officers
report to administration
before the end of shift.
[door squeaks, clangs shut]
- [buzzer sounds]
- [lock clangs]
- [door clangs]
- [lock clicks]
Eleven o'clock.
Red jacket.
[newscaster on TV]
Breaking news.
A tragedy at the home
of late mob boss
- Carmine Falcone...
- Hey, come on!
Some of us got places to be.
...Sofia Falcone,
Carmine's daughter,
is currently one of the only
confirmed survivors.
GCPD has yet to release
any results
of their still-early
investigation,
but these deaths follow
a period of intense violence
between the Falcone and
the Maroni crime families.
[dramatic, uneasy music playing]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[music darkens]
[man] Ms. Falcone?
Please, I prefer Sofia.
Police Chief Bock.
Gotham City Police Department.
[reporters] Ms. Falcone!
[reporters clamoring]
Can we, um...?
Yeah.
[helicopter whirring overhead]
You said you remained
in the greenhouse all night.
Gia and I, yes.
There was an argument
between my Uncle Luca
and my cousin Johnny.
Carla asked me
to take Gia outside...
keep her away from it.
[Bock] What was the argument
about?
[vehicle drives off]
I, uh, only heard
bits and pieces.
Something about Luca's wife,
Tina.
There were rumors
about an affair, but I, uh...
It wasn't a good situation
for a young girl to be in.
Johnny Viti's
not among the dead.
Any idea where
we might find him?
I'm sorry, no.
He must've left last night.
I didn't come back inside
until this morning.
And that's when I, uh...
[whispers] ...saw the bodies.
Excuse me.
Awfully suspicious,
don't you think?
Prominent crime family in Gotham
wiped out by a gas leak?
[uneasy music playing]
Is that a question
you'd like me to answer?
Tell me,
is it common for
the chief of police
to respond to house calls?
We are quite a ways
from the city.
I hope you didn't come
to my home
to throw my family's death
in my face.
It's a new era in Gotham,
Ms. Falcone.
The mayor-elect's got a mandate
to put an end
to the scum of this city.
So you're here to see it
for yourself.
Hmm?
And I suppose you and your boys
are gonna go for beers later?
To celebrate?
Maybe swap photos
of my dead relatives?
Or are you going to sell those
to the Gazette
to make up for all
the lost kickbacks?
We're doing our due diligence.
If you hear from Johnny Viti,
give us a call.
Sorry for your loss.
[bird calling]
[liquid sloshing]
- [door opens]
- [Viti breathing shakily]
[door closes]
- [footsteps approaching]
- [keys jingling]
[grunting]
[Sofia] The cops are
looking for you, Johnny.
Although I get the sense they'd
rather find you dead than alive.
[panting]
You're not looking too good.
[groans]
[breathing rapidly]
[pained grunts]
The fuck is wrong with you?
You're fucking sick.
What kind of person kills
their own fuckin' family?
- I need untraceable cash.
- [sighs]
I know that my father would have
kept it somewhere close.
And all you gotta do is show me.
- And then I'll let you go.
- Right.
[chuckles]
You think I'm a fuckin' idiot?
The second I do what you want,
you fucking kill me.
So just fuckin' do it already.
Oh, please, Johnny.
You're not that brave.
But if you need more time
to think, you got it.
[chains rattling]
Although you should know,
it gets very cold down here.
And with the work that it takes
your body
to keep your organs alive...
[ominous music playing]
...you won't last long.
Wait!
[screams]
[newscaster] Several members
of the Falcone family
are still reported missing,
including Johnny Viti...
[Eve] She knows you
killed her brother,
and now she's gassed
her entire family.
[Oz] Doll, let's relax.
[Eve] Don't tell me to relax.
I was your alibi, Oz.
You made me that.
Keep your voice down, alright?
The guys don't know
all the details.
You got too many plates
spinning.
Listen, sweetheart, I know
you can't see it right now,
but all this shit goin' down,
it's a good thing.
I put it all in motion.
Luca, the Family...
Sofia just took the bait,
that's all.
Baby, do you even know when
you're full of shit anymore?
- Huh?
- Me and the girls.
You dangled us in front of her.
- I didn't dangle you.
- You think it's a good thing?
The Hangman knowing
their names, their faces...
She's gunning for us now.
While Taj Maroni sits
in my apartment.
[Oz] The fuck
was I supposed to do?
They stole my shit.
Come on, doll.
Nothing's gonna happen to you.
I won't let it.
All I'm askin' is for you to
hang tight just a little longer.
That's it.
And then it's you and me
on top of the world, baby.
I need you to fix this.
That's what I do. I fix things.
Don't I fix things? Huh?
[newscaster] ...there is no
threat to rescue workers...
That's all I ever fuckin' do.
[newscaster] As of now,
GCPD has yet to confirm
- the total deceased...
- Members of Falcone family dead.
Boo-hoo-hoo. Turn that shit off.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Look.
I know this shit's grim,
but none of those fucks
were friends of ours.
They never made us.
Luca Falcone didn't even know
your fuckin' names.
So who ya missing?
That skinny little pussy,
Johnny Viti?
Milos?
Guy wore lifts in his shoes.
We all knew it.
The way I see it,
Sofia done us a favor.
- One family down, one to go.
- [men chuckling]
Now, let's get back what
belongs to us, alright?
- [man 1] All right.
- Get the fuck out.
- [man 2] Let's go, brother.
- [Oz] Let's do it.
Hey, come on.
You. Come here.
[man 1] Come on.
I'm gonna need you with my ma.
- Oz, I thought I'd, uh...
- [door closes]
...be with you and the guys.
I'm ready, I swear--
I know you wanna get
in the fight, kid,
but I ain't got no one else
I can trust, and look.
Sofia's gonna come for us.
Whether it's today or tomorrow,
she's gonna do whatever the fuck
it takes, and I can't have--
I mean, my ma, she's,
you know...
She's what keeps me good.
I gotta know she's alright.
Yeah. Done.
I'm gonna...
I'll-I'll take care of her.
I promise.
[Bruno] Hold still,
stop squirming.
- Get him up.
- [Taj grunting]
[tense music playing]
Let's get you home.
[door opens]
[music fades]
[Viti shivering]
[exhales]
How you doing, Johnny?
[sinister music playing]
You ready to head back
to the house?
Maybe warm yourself
by a nice fire,
light an expensive cigar?
[Viti coughing]
Or...
do you want to die
down here in the dark,
with all the greats?
[Viti panting, coughing]
I can't guarantee you'll get
one of these, uh,
gold nameplates,
but I'm sure we can find you
a very nice unmarked hole
somewhere.
She-She was gonna leave him,
you know...
The night Isabella died.
She was gonna leave Carmine.
Don't talk about my mother.
[Viti] You remember, don't you?
You were all packed
and ready to go.
She was gonna take you
and your brother on a trip.
That's what she told you.
She was my cousin.
I loved her.
She asked for my help.
I had a fucking car waiting
a few blocks down the road
and she never fuckin' showed.
[Viti choking]
You are a desperate
fucking liar.
I swear.
I got no reason to lie anymore!
[Viti coughs]
I ain't tryin' to push
on a bruise, Sofia.
She was with Carmine
'cause of me.
You knew that, right?
I introduced them.
And your father.
He was smitten
right outta the gate.
God, she was beautiful,
your mom.
[emotional, uneasy music
playing]
She was so beautiful.
She had that laugh.
When you got her going,
it'd knock you out.
[laughs softly]
She couldn't take it anymore
being his wife.
She just fucking
couldn't take it.
She tried to leave once before,
but she came right back.
She came right back
'cause of you fucking kids.
Would've been so much
easier for her
if it weren't
for the two of you.
[music darkens]
[barrel scraping]
[Viti shivering]
[Viti] I wi...
Sometimes, I wish...
It's done.
What's done is... [shivers]
What's done is done.
What he did is done.
[sighs, shivers]
But you kept on working for him.
You loved her so much, you were
his underboss for years.
Yeah.
- [Viti sighs, shivers]
- Yeah.
But you need me now, Sofia.
You need me.
You wanna be boss?
You wanna win this war?
Then money's not enough.
You need respect.
You need soldiers
who want to fight for you.
You go it alone out there,
you're not gonna last a day.
I can get you that respect.
I couldn't help your mother.
Let me help you.
[Viti gasping]
Come on.
[lock clicking]
[TV playing indistinctly]
Mrs. Cobb?
[woman on TV]
What are you gonna do?
Shoot a six-year-old kid...
- [door closes, lock clicks]
- It's...
- [engine revs on TV]
- [man exclaims on TV]
[tires screeching on TV]
- Mrs. Cobb, it's... it's Victor.
- [gunfire on TV]
- [TV audio mutes]
- Francis?
[uneasy music playing]
[faint hissing]
[whispers] Oh my God...
- [pots clanging]
- [Victor reacts in pain]
[hissing stops]
[uneasy music continues]
- Mrs. Cobb?
- [music fades]
Hey.
- [Victor] Hi.
- Hey. There you are.
[laughs] Why are you
way over there?
Come here, sweetheart.
Come here. [laughs]
Look what I found.
You remember this?
Um... no.
No, ma'am.
It's your glove
from Little League.
- Look how small--
- I'm sorry. I'm...
I'm V... [stammers]
I'm V-Victor.
I'm Victor.
[stutters] I-I work with Oz.
Oswald... Right? Your son?
He-He s-sent me here
to ch-check up on you.
I know who you are.
I tell my son to visit more,
so he sends strangers.
I get it.
Well, help me up
for Christ's sake.
Uh, okay, here we go.
Whoa, whoa.
What is this?
What? I don't know.
Oh, shit. Well...
I fell.
Maybe I was pushed. [laughs]
So...
- Nurse boy.
- [Victor groans]
What's Oswald doin' that's more
important than me? Huh?
He's making a move, um...
against the Maronis.
- Maronis?
- [food thuds in garbage can]
No, baby, you got it backwards.
He's workin' them to get
at the Falcones.
- [plate clatters]
- They're the bigger fish.
They're all dead.
Was it him? Did Oswald kill 'em?
Yeah.
Don't lie to me.
You're bad at it.
It's the truth.
Oz...
Oz pulled this off.
That's why I'm here right now,
to... to...
m-make sure that you're safe
while this is all going down.
[Francis] Finally.
Okay, then. [sniffles]
So...
he's gonna need
my help then, right?
Okay, let's go! Let's do this!
Let's... [cackles]
[dramatic music playing]
[prisoners clamoring]
[prisoner yelling indistinctly]
[tap running]
[cell door sliding]
- [tap stops]
- [approaching footsteps]
[Mikey] This is from Oz, motherfucker.
- [grunting]
- [suspenseful music plays]
[Salvatore groaning]
[music fades]
[engine stops]
Nadia, Nadia, Nadia.
Always a pleasure.
My son. Now.
Straight to business, huh?
You know, I respect that.
- Bruno.
- [van door opens]
[thudding in van]
[Oz] C'mere.
[muffled grunting]
[Oz] Jesus.
Stop fuckin' shakin'.
[van door creaks shut]
What have you done to him?
He's fine. Picture of health.
Remove the tape.
I want to hear it from him.
I'm doing you a solid.
Your son's a talker.
We all want this over quick.
Just lemme see the shrooms,
and we'll be on our way.
- [Taj grunting]
- [liquid dripping]
Bruno. Check the product.
[tense music playing]
- [muffled whimpers]
- Calm down.
- Relax. Jesus Christ.
- [liquid dripping]
We're good.
Alright, Nadia.
My friend Bruno,
he's gonna get in that truck--
That truck stays put...
until my son is released.
Relax, Nadia.
I know.
Go to Mama.
[muffled grunting]
[breathing heavily]
So sorry...
- [gate closing]
- [alarm blaring]
- [Oz] Fuck!
- [suspenseful music plays]
[gunfire]
[grunting]
[Taj grunting]
- [gunfire continues]
- [man grunts]
[grunting]
[lighter clicks]
- [Nadia] Baby...
- [Taj] Mom.
Oh, no.
Oh, shit!
[Taj screaming]
[Taj continues screaming]
[tense, dramatic music playing]
[both screaming]
[screaming continues]
[fire suppressors hissing]
[alarm ringing]
[hissing]
[Oz] Fuck! The shrooms!
Get in the truck!
- Go, go, go!
- [tires screeching]
["De Do Do Do, De Da Da Da"
by The Police playing]
♪ ...Their logic ties you up
and rapes you ♪
♪ De do do do, de da da da ♪
♪ Is all I want to say to you ♪
♪ Their innocence
will pull me through ♪
♪ De do do do, de da da da ♪
- [music stops]
- [Nick] Shit, what happened?
- You alright?
- [Bruno] It was fucked up, man.
They tried to screw us.
Oz lit 'em up...
[conversation continues
indistinctly]
No, no, no.
No!
No, no, no...
No.
No!
Fuckin' dead.
Fuck.
They're all fuckin' dead!
That's it?!
Oz? What-What's the matter?
They're ruined.
We got two buckets.
That's fuckin' it!
The rest are fucked!
You don't build a goddamn empire
with two fuckin' buckets!
- We can't get more?
- More?
- Yeah.
- From where, Nick? Huh?
Sofia's been working this shit
for months.
Take these to the truck.
Get this shit.
Crank up the heat.
Keep 'em warm.
[phone buzzing]
[Nick] Put them in the back
of the van.
I'll start the engine
and turn on the heat.
Mikey, tell me somethin' good.
[Salvatore] Mikey's dead,
you little bitch.
[ominous music playing]
Thanks for the keys, Oz.
I never coulda busted out
without 'em.
[scoffs] You amateur
piece of shit.
There's no place
I can't find you now.
No place, Oz!
You are cooked.
Cooked, huh?
That's funny.
Do me a favor, Sal.
Call your wife.
See if she answers.
You stole
from the wrong fucking guy.
- [music fades]
- [panting]
Fuck.
[line ringing]
- [Victor] Oz.
- How is she?
Yeah, uh, no,
she's-she's... she's...
She's f--
Vic, how is she?!
She's fine.
She's just-- She's sleeping.
When you gonna be here?
Look, I got a lotta heat on me.
So, uh...
I need you to get my ma
outta there, alright?
There's a go bag in the kitchen,
it's behind the vent,
in the pantry.
Take it and whatever else
you can get. Her meds.
Don't forget her fucking meds!
She ain't gonna like it much.
- You seen how she can get.
- Wh...
- What happened?
- Goddammit, Vic!
Just do it, alright?
W-Well, where do we go?
[uneasy music playing]
I don't know.
It's gotta be somewhere
where nobody'd think to look.
You know?
Just, uh... Just get in the car.
Right? And just drive.
Okay, yeah.
I'll-I'll-I'll-I'll...
[breathes rapidly]
I'll find a place that's safe.
And, uh, I'll call you
when I get there, alright?
- Yeah, good, good.
- Okay. Hey, Oz.
I got this, okay?
I'm gonna take care of her.
Yeah, you do that.
[music fades]
[birds singing]
[sniffing softly]
["Reckless" by St. Vincent
playing]
[knocking]
Yes?
[Julian] Sofia...
[door closes]
What are you doing here?
[Julian] The police came to me,
asking about you.
[Sofia] Hmm.
I didn't say anything.
What do you want, Julian?
Because I'm in the middle
of something,
and I think we're past the point
of analysis, don't you?
Yes.
You're right.
And you were right about me.
But it's not the control I miss.
When I saw what happened
on the news,
I knew it was you.
That you did what you had to do.
I can already see it,
what it's given you.
The release.
And I'd like to feel that, too.
With you.
I'd like to be a part
of whatever's next...
[music builds]
...if you'll have me.
[music intensifies]
[men chattering]
♪ Calling for me ♪
[Viti] Hey!
Quiet the fuck down.
The lady's got something to say.
["Reckless" continues playing]
♪ Calling for me ♪
[Sofia] Thank you, Johnny.
[Viti] Sit down.
[music fades]
[Viti clears throat]
[Sofia] First,
I'd like to address
the elephant in the room.
I gassed the Family.
[man whispers] Oh, Jesus Christ.
I killed them all.
And I am
so glad
that they're dead.
My family disposed of my mother
like she was nothing.
Then they did the same to me.
And honestly,
none of you
are any different.
None of you are made men.
Except for Johnny here.
[kisses]
The rest of you...
[inhales sharply]
You're pawns.
You're overlooked.
Expendable.
[uneasy music playing]
My mother was Isabella Gigante.
[inhales shakily]
Few spoke of her after she died,
because she was a force
greater than the Falcones
could handle.
As of today,
my father's legacy is dead
and we will never speak
his name again.
From this point on,
I am a Gigante,
and this is a new Family now.
[hushed] What are you doing?
A family that will not treat you
like cannon fodder
in a fruitless war
against the Maronis.
A war which I intend to end.
Alright, okay, Sofia.
Let's not be rash here.
These gentlemen know
we got a score
we need to settle--
[men gasping]
[whispering indistinctly]
[Sofia] Hmm.
[Sofia huffs]
This.
This was my father's.
But he made it off
of your labor.
You did the dirty work
and they kept it all
for themselves.
If you join me,
you will have a new Family.
And I'll pay you
what you're worth.
More money than
you've ever seen before.
[tense music playing]
[inhales deeply]
[sighs]
Ms. Gigante?
Go ahead.
[dramatic music playing]
[dramatic music swells,
fades out]
- [siren wailing]
- [car horn honking]
- [siren continues]
- [car horns honking]
[siren chirping]
[kids chattering]
[Francis] Why are we here?
You said Oswald was takin' over.
Yeah, he is, but, uh...
He said things
with the Maronis got messy
and that we should go somewhere
no one would think to look.
[man] All right, let's go.
Clean 'em out. Take everything.
Whatever's left of this
fucking shithole.
[indistinct chatter]
No one really cares about
Crown Point, so...
[engine stops]
[hip-hop music playing
in background]
[distant siren wailing]
[car door opens]
Ain't this nice.
VIP parkin'.
[man] We're gonna smash
this shit right here.
- Grab everything that's left.
- [glass smashing]
Don't leave nothin' in there.
Clean the whole
fuckin' place out.
[glass clinking]
Shit.
[bottles clinking]
[whispers] Hey. Whoa.
Don't let 'em see you, okay?
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
- Come on.
- What did he do to you?
You're practically
pissin' yourself.
Please. Shut up. Shut up.
Shut up.
Come here, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Please.
His name...
His name is S-Squid.
He's a bad guy.
He runs, uh, Drops and all
the other stuff in this area.
Listen, Francis.
We gotta get off of the street
right now, okay?
That's where we're headed.
You ready?
[glass clinking]
[Francis] Where are you
takin' me?
[Victor] My friend Calvin's
apartment.
He used to live here.
Watch your step.
It's been condemned.
Come on.
[hip-hop music
continues faintly]
[ominous music playing]
[music fades]
[door hinge creaking]
No lights, huh?
Yeah.
[Francis sighs]
[Francis] Wow.
[Victor] What is it?
What's wrong?
This looks like the apartment
I had with my boys.
I hate it here.
[soft, melancholy music playing]
I used to live over there.
[sighs]
The Eastside is cursed.
It takes everything from you.
[subway clattering]
[indistinct yelling]
[whistling]
[pounding on door]
[soft pop music playing
on stereo]
You alone?
- What's wrong?
- [lock clicks]
[breathing rapidly]
Oz, baby.
What have they done to you?
- Hey. Hey. Okay.
- Come here.
[Eve] It's okay. It's okay.
[Oz] Alright, get your things.
Come on.
We gotta lay low.
Vic's already in Crown Point.
He's got us a nice spot
by the Zoo.
Crown Point?
What are you talking about?
I know it ain't perfect.
It's the only place
Sal and Sofia got no pull.
Sal? Oh my God, Oz.
There's something else.
Before we go, I gotta tell ya.
It ain't just me and Vic, alright?
Yeah, but, Oz.
I'm not-- I'm not going
with you.
I can't.
I thought we was
in this together.
Un-fuckin'-believable,
you're doing this right now.
Where you gonna go, huh?
You got some high roller
you'd rather shack up with, huh?
- For the money?
- Oz. Baby.
We had a deal.
We look out for each other.
We don't fuck each other over.
That's why this worked.
It ain't--
After everything I done for you?
It ain't fucking workin'
no more?
Huh? After everything
I fucking done for you?
Jesus fucking Christ!
Fuck.
I'm a fuckin' idiot!
- Fuckin' dumb.
- Okay, okay. Shh.
- Stupid. Stupid.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
[ominous music playing]
You're onto something, baby.
I know you gonna be
on top again soon.
You know I'm yours.
But right now, I'm just...
I'm just gonna hold you back.
[exhales, sighs]
- [insects chirring]
- [music fades]
[vehicle approaching]
[crying softly]
[sniffles]
[vehicle doors open]
[man] Shit! Around the back!
- [gunfire outside]
- [man yells in pain]
- [gunshot]
- [body thuds]
[door closes]
Freedom always comes at a cost,
doesn't it?
[grunting in pain]
Sit down, Salvatore.
What a funky hideout.
Big fan of wood, I see.
Ooh!
Oh, Antonucci's.
Oh, that doesn't look like
it traveled well.
My father always said you were
too sentimental.
That it made you weak.
I don't think he understood
why you cared so much
about your family.
That's because you Falcones
eat your own.
Your family had it right,
I think.
Ten years ago,
some measly driver
spun a bullshit story about me.
He betrayed me,
the daughter of the Falcone Don,
and he got rewarded for it.
And now here we are.
Both of us suffering
at the hands of that same man.
[breathes shakily]
But you...
Would you have let that stand?
[scoffs]
I woulda ripped out his tongue
and left him for the vultures.
That's what I thought.
I'm very sorry about your wife
and son, Salvatore.
Why are you here?
What do you want?
I've come here to end the war
between our Families.
[exhales]
[tense music playing]
I'm not gonna kill you.
Why?
Because it's what Oz wants.
Ah, Falcones and Maronis
have been--
The Falcones
don't exist anymore.
I am offering you an alliance.
We join our families,
the Maronis and Gigantes,
as a show of strength.
We kill Oz.
And then we take over the city.
[dramatic music builds]
Together.
[music fades]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[distant siren wailing]
[bed frame squeaks]
[Oz whispers softly]
Oswald...
[softly] I'm sorry, Ma.
I feel like I let you down.
You did.
This place is temporary.
- I got...
- [chuckles]
I just gotta figure out
my next move.
Yep.
My boy... [sniffles]
With such big dreams.
[Oz chuckles]
Like your father.
No, Ma.
I ain't like him.
- I can fix this.
- [Francis murmurs]
It's you and me
under one roof now.
Like it used to be.
Are you're tryin' to kill me?
No, Ma,
I'm tryin' to protect you.
It's better this way,
when we're together.
Takin' me back here,
you're throwin' it in my face...
what I lost.
I lost 'em too.
[Francis sniffles]
What kind of man can't take care
of his own mother?
Get off.
Get off!
[sniffling]
[sighs]
[door closes]
[glass clinking]
[objects clattering]
[Victor] I'm awake.
[Oz] Hey.
[exhales] Fuck. Oz...
Shit. I fell asleep.
Alright, I'm--
[Oz] Stop.
You did good, kid.
I know you don't wanna be
here neither.
It was a smart move.
Crown Point.
[traffic hums outside]
[distant siren wailing]
[people chattering outside]
Told her I'd get her
a penthouse.
The best view in the city.
[Victor] She s-said that
you guys
kinda lived near here?
[Oz] Two-bedroom walk-up.
Looked a helluva lot
like this fuckin' dump.
[chuckles]
This was Jack's.
Benny didn't play ball.
[Victor] What happened to 'em?
To your brothers?
The city took 'em.
Just like it took your family.
There was nothin' I could...
I was, uh...
too weak.
My brothers and me, we used to
get into all kinds of trouble.
Back then, when we was kids,
we just had the city, you know?
That was our playground.
["A Forest" by The Cure playing]
Hey, kid.
Let's go.
[helicopter whirring overhead]
[Oz] You ever heard of
the underground trolleys?
Used to run here.
[Victor] No.
[light buzzing]
[barking]
[dog continues barking]
[metal clanging]
[metal screeching]
[metal chain snaps]
[metal clanging]
[hinge creaking]
[Oz] Me and my brothers,
we used to mess around
down here a lot.
These tunnels,
they go everywhere.
Gave us access to
the whole damn city.
Come on.
How long have these been here?
[Oz] They were abandoned
when I was a kid.
Politicians got greedy.
Diverted funds.
One day, the trolleys
just stopped runnin'.
["A Forest" continues playing]
[liquid dripping]
[Oz] Wow...
Long time.
[Victor] Wow. Holy shit.
Fuckin' unbelievable, right?
[generator sputtering]
[generator whirring]
[laughing]
Huh?
[Victor] Whoa...
[dramatic music playing]
[Oz] It's gonna take some work,
you know, to get it into shape,
but once we do...
Hey, kid!
You feel that, right?
It's humid down here, dark.
You know what thrives
in a place like this?
- Mushrooms?
- Bingo.
Yeah, mushrooms.
Welcome to our new
base of operations.
[chuckles]
This fuckin' place...
callin' me home.
[generator sputtering]
[dramatic music swells]
- [electricity crackles]
- [bulb explodes]
[generator sputters, stops]
["Reckless" by St. Vincent
playing]
♪ And I've been
mourning you since ♪
♪ The day I met you ♪
♪ And a stranger come
in my path ♪
♪ And I'll eat you up, I ♪
♪ I tear you limb from limb ♪
♪ Or I'll fall in love ♪
♪ Reckless, reckless ♪
♪ Reckless ♪
♪ If your love was an anchor ♪
♪ And I am lost at sea ♪
♪ I hear the riders calling ♪
♪ They're calling for me ♪
♪ Calling for me ♪
[mysterious theme music playing]
[music fades]